May 17, 2017

Dear BurnAlong Team,

I am writing to express interest in the Front-End Web Developer position at BurnAlong.

During my 18 years experience as a Web Designer and Front End Developer at R2integrated, DuClaw Brewing Company, North Charles Street Design Organization and the University of Maryland Baltimore County, I have honed my skills in web development using Wordpress, CSS/SASS, HTML, and JQuery. I have collaborated with art directors to deliver fully-functioning web sites within strict deadlines.

I am excited for the opportunity to be a part of BurnAlong's growth, and to build the mobile team. This position will provide the chance to apply my skills, and learn some new skills as well, such as mobile app development.

Please visit <u>www.aaronweidele.com</u> to see examples of my work. If I may answer any additional questions for you, please do not hesitate to contact me at 443.207.1468 or at aweidele@gmail.com. Thank you for your time and consideration, and I look forward to speaking with you soon.

Sincerely,

Aaron Weidele

SKILLS

Responsive web design

HTML, CSS/SASS/LESS

PHP

Javascript/JQuery

Wordpress

Sitecore

Git

SourceTree

Jira

Shopify

MailChimp + MailChimp API

MySQL

PayPal/Payflow

Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Premiere, After Effects, Flash)

Web prototyping tools (Axure, Balsamic, HotGloo)

UX Design

Usability Testing

Motion Graphics

Experience with Google Analytics

EDUCATION

1995-2000

University of Maryland Baltimore County / B.A. Imaging and Digital Arts

WORK EXPERIENCE

2016-Present Front-End Developer, R2integrated

Collaborated with designers, back-end developers, and QA to build websites and components in Sitecore

Built framework for future Sitecore projects to facilitate faster development

2014–2016 Front-End Developer, DuClaw Brewing Company

Worked with designers to develop microsites for festivals and special beer releases

Developed distributor order forms using PHP and MySQL

Migrated web store to Shopify, and set up Shopify POS for merchandise sales at festivals

2010–2014 Interactive Designer, North Charles Street Design Organization

Design and development of interactive recruitment campaigns for higher education. Campaigns included an email series and landing site.

Build custom Wordpress themes for advancement campaign websites.

Motion graphics for digital signs

Awards:

Gold Award / New Media / Higher Education Marketing Report's 27th Annual Educational Advertising Awards

Silver Award / Website / Higher Education Marketing Report's 26th Annual Educational Advertising Awards

Silver Award / Video Viewbook / Higher Education Marketing Report's 26th Annual Educational Advertising Awards

1999–2010 New Media Specialist, University of Maryland Baltimore County

Designed websites for university departments

Developed online Undergraduate Catalog

Developed online interactive campus map

Trained faculty and staff in content management

Presentations:

New Media Consortium / 2009 / Monterey, CA /

Poster presentation, "Finding Your Career Path," about the Career Path web site

New Media Consortium / 2005 / Honolulu, HI / 5 Minutes of Fame, "Building a Campus Map," a 5-minute presentation on building the interactive campus map of UMBC